<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="info">Mobile Apps www.apssdc.in are becoming popular day by day. Today, Everyone owns a smartphone and they do a lot of things with the help of their smartphones such as making payments, ordering groceries, playing games, chatting with friends and colleagues etc .There is huge demand in the market to develop android apps. It’s Google’s CEO Sundar Pichai\'s initiative to train 2 Million people to become android developers as this platform has a huge need of developers. In view of this scenario and keeping industry needs in mind, APSSDC is offering “Android Application Development - FDP” so that the faculty across engineering colleges in the state of Andhra Pradesh gain App Development knowledge and share the same to their students.\n\n
    Mobile Apps are becoming popular day by day. Today, Everyone owns a smartphone and they do a lot of things with the help of their smartphones such as making payments, ordering groceries, playing games, chatting with friends and colleagues etc .There is huge demand in the market to develop android apps. It’s Google’s CEO Sundar Pichai\'s initiative to train 2 Million people to become android developers as this platform has a huge need of developers. In view of this scenario and keeping industry needs in mind, APSSDC is offering “Android Application Development - FDP” so that the faculty across engineering colleges in the state of Andhra Pradesh gain App Development knowledge and share the same to their students.\n\n
    Mobile Apps are becoming popular day by day. Today, Everyone owns a smartphone 9874561230 and they do a lot of things with the help of their smartphones such as making payments, ordering groceries, playing games, chatting with friends and colleagues etc .There is huge demand in the market to develop android apps. It’s Google’s CEO Sundar Pichai\'s initiative to train 2 Million people to become android developers as this platform has a huge need of developers. In view of this scenario and keeping industry needs in mind, APSSDC is offering “Android Application Development - FDP” so that the faculty across engineering colleges in the state of Andhra Pradesh gain App Development knowledge and share the same to their students.\n\n
    /nMobile Apps are becoming popular day by day. Today, Everyone owns a smartphone and they do a lot of things with the help of their smartphones such as making payments, ordering groceries, playing games, muneiah.t@apssdc.in chatting with friends and colleagues etc .There is huge demand in the market to develop android apps. It’s Google’s CEO Sundar Pichai\'s initiative to train 2 Million people to become android developers as this platform has a huge need of developers. In view of this scenario and keeping industry needs in mind, APSSDC is offering “Android Application Development - FDP” so that the faculty across engineering colleges in the state of Andhra Pradesh gain App Development knowledge and share the same to their students.</string>
    <string name="about">Hello I\'m Muneiah Tellkula From APssdc</string>
</resources>